907 Forest Drive, Garner, NC 27529 (919) 921-7562 massengillashley@icloud.com ashleymassengill.github.io

ashlevmassengill.com

## **OVERVIEW**

Through my experiences, I have learned where my strengths lie. I enjoy writing code and turning designs into interactive products through HTML and CSS. My goal is to continue growing my experience and knowledge in ways that allow me to tap into the creative and organized sides of my personality to create a product that is the best outcome for everyone.

#### **STRENGTHS**

★ Creative Thinking

★ Great Eye for Detail

★ Analytical Thinking

★ Extreme Efficiency

★ Teaching Skills

★ Organization

#### PROJECT HISTORY

UI Designer & Developer, diaBEATthis

[i] Jan 2017

(\$) Raleigh, NC

diaBEATthis is a website and web app focused on assisting diabetes suferers track and manage the various aspects of their disease. As the sole visual designer for diaBEATthis, was responsible for designing, developing and coding the style guide, branding, and page layouts. Tech: Illustrator, Photoshop, Atom, iTerm, HTML5, SASS, Skeleton, jQuery, Github

#### UI Developer,

Nov 2016

Raleigh, NC

#### Treasures Unearthed

Treasures Unearthed is a virtual exhibit of the North Carolina Museum of Natural Science, Was part of a three person team, responsible for creating visual design, content, layout, and branding. Responsible for coding all navigation features, interactive map, and media queries.

Tech: Atom, iTerm, HTML5, SASS, Skeleton, jQuery, GitHub

# UI Designer & Developer,

Nov 2016

Raleigh, NC

## Goodreads Bookshelf Redesign

Goodreads is an Amazon owned personal reading list management site. The design is dated and confusing, calling for a complete redesign. Focusing on the personal bookshelf feature, sole designer and developer of rebranding, features, and layout as well as all coding.

Tech: Atom, iTerm, HTML5, SASS, jQuery, GitHub

#### **WORK HISTORY**

Database Manager, RCI, Inc.

i Apr 2016 - Jul 2016

- Managed internal tech support including computer hardware, software, phone systems, servers, and website.
- Guided implementation of new AMS through search, demon, contract, setup and testing phases into training and go-live.
- Created and maintained all reporting operations for each department.

#### Meetings Specialist, RCI, Inc.

i Dec 2010 - Apr 2016

(\$) Raleigh, NC

- Produced event based website layouts and coding.
- Managed all event registrations for 10+ attendee events to 1500+ attedee events.
- Created all meeting collateral for international events from general education to conventions and trade shows.

#### Customer Relations Manager, North Carolina Chamber

i Aug 2007 - Mar 2010

(\$) Raleigh, NC

#### • Database management, including ensuring data accuracy.

- Internal IT support in collaboration with external IT team.
- Processed all event registrations and assisted in minor logistics.
- Created and maintained all company-wide reporting processes and data analytics.

# **TECHNOLOGIES**

CSS3 HTMI 5

SASS

**iQuery** 

Atom

Skeleton

Bootstrap

GitHub

Windows

iTerm

Mac OS

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe InDesign

Adobe Photoshop

Microsoft Office

Trello

Apple iWork

Google Docs

Crystal Reports

## **VOLUNTEER HISTORY**

Adobe Acrobat

**Guest Services** NC State Athletics

🗓 Aug 2016 - current

Raleigh, NC

Box Office & Boutique Assistant Carolina Ballet

🗓 Aug 2010 - current

Raleigh, NC

Admissions & Ticketing Services USGA Men's & Women's US Open

ii) Jul 2014

(\$) Pinehurst, NC

**Event Assistant** SPARKcon

Sept 2009

Raleigh, NC

#### **EDUCATION**

UI Design, The Iron Yard

i Oct 2016 - Jan 2017

Raleigh, NC

## East Carolina University

🗓 Aug 2001 - May 2003 💲 Greenville, NC

# **INTERESTS**



Dogs













